tpg.com 2019-03-17

# TPG WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY Last modified: May 2018 Our Commitment to Your Privacy This Privacy Policy applies to www.tpg.com , www.tpgspecialtylendingeurope.com, and tpgspecialtylending.com (together, the “Site”), which provides information about the affiliated entities commonly referred to as “TPG”. This privacy policy only applies to information we may collect from visitors to the Site or that visitors to the Site may provide through the Site. Information We Collect This Site does not directly collect any personal information. You may, however, chose to contact us by email, in which case we will collect your name, email address and any other information that you chose to provide to us. Please do not provide personal information that you do not want us to have. In addition, we may gather information about you automatically through your use of the Site, e.g., your IP address and how you navigate our Site. TPG may collect information about you by using cookies, tracking pixels and other technologies (collectively, “Tools”). We may use this information to better understand, customize and improve the user experience of our websites, services and offerings. For example, we may use web analytics services such as Google Analytics that leverage Tools to help us understand how visitors engage with and navigate our Site. Information on how Google Analytics collects and processes your data is available here: www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. Your web browser can be set to allow you to control whether you will accept cookies, reject cookies, or to notify you each time a cookie is sent to you. If your browser is set to reject cookies, the Site may not recognize you when you return to the website, and some website functionality may be lost. The Help section of your browser may tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage or delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org. How We Use the Information We Collect If you choose to provide information to us, for example by email, the information is used for the purpose you provided it to us. For example, if you provide your contact information in an inquiry to us, we will use your contact information to process and respond to that inquiry and any related activity that may result from your inquiry. How We Share the Information We Collect We may share your personal information with TPG Global, LLC and its affiliates for the purposes described in this Policy. We may share personal information with service providers that perform services on our behalf such as payment service providers, analytics providers, and hosting providers. In accordance with applicable law, we have entered into legally binding agreements requiring

TPG WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
Last modified: May 2018
Our Commitment to Your Privacy
This Privacy Policy applies to www.tpg.com , www.tpgspecialtylendingeurope.com, and
tpgspecialtylending.com (together, the “Site”), which provides information about the
affiliated entities commonly referred to as “TPG”. This privacy policy only applies to
information we may collect from visitors to the Site or that visitors to the Site may provide
through the Site.
Information We Collect
This Site does not directly collect any personal information. You may, however, chose to
contact us by email, in which case we will collect your name, email address and any other
information that you chose to provide to us. Please do not provide personal information that
you do not want us to have.
In addition, we may gather information about you automatically through your use of the Site,
e.g., your IP address and how you navigate our Site. TPG may collect information about you
by using cookies, tracking pixels and other technologies (collectively, “Tools”). We may use
this information to better understand, customize and improve the user experience of our
websites, services and offerings. For example, we may use web analytics services such as
Google Analytics that leverage Tools to help us understand how visitors engage with and
navigate our Site. Information on how Google Analytics collects and processes your data is
available here: www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.
Your web browser can be set to allow you to control whether you will accept cookies, reject
cookies, or to notify you each time a cookie is sent to you. If your browser is set to reject
cookies, the Site may not recognize you when you return to the website, and some website
functionality may be lost. The Help section of your browser may tell you how to prevent your
browser from accepting cookies. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what
cookies have been set and how to manage or delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
How We Use the Information We Collect
If you choose to provide information to us, for example by email, the information is used for
the purpose you provided it to us. For example, if you provide your contact information in an
inquiry to us, we will use your contact information to process and respond to that inquiry and
any related activity that may result from your inquiry.
How We Share the Information We Collect
We may share your personal information with TPG Global, LLC and its affiliates for the
purposes described in this Policy.
We may share personal information with service providers that perform services on our
behalf such as payment service providers, analytics providers, and hosting providers. In
accordance with applicable law, we have entered into legally binding agreements requiring

them to use or disclose personal information only as necessary to perform services on our
behalf or comply with applicable legal requirements.
In addition, we may disclose personal information about you (a) if we are required or
permitted to do so by law or legal process, for example due to a court order or a request from
a law enforcement agency, (b) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to
prevent physical harm or financial loss, (c) in connection with an investigation of suspected
or actual fraudulent or other illegal activity, and (d) in conjunction with (i) the making,
management, or disposition of any of our investments, or (ii) business continuity.
Links to Third-Party Websites
The Site may contain links to other web sites. We have no control over and are not
responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such sites. Whenever you link to another
web site, you may be asked to provide registration or other information. Please note that any
information that you provide is going to a third party, and therefore you should familiarize
yourself with that party’s privacy policy.
Data Transfers
The Site is controlled and operated from the United States and is not intended to be subject to
the laws or jurisdiction of any country or territory other than that of the United States.
Information Security
We maintain appropriate technical and organisational measures designed to protect your
personal information against loss or accidental, unlawful or unauthorised, alteration, access,
disclosure or use. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to
be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer
secure, please notify us immediately.
Do Not Track
Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When
a user turns on DNT, the browser sends a message to websites requesting that they do not
track the user. TPG does not change its practices, described elsewhere in this privacy policy,
in response to DNT browser settings or signals. For information about DNT, visit
www.allaboutdnt.org.
Third parties may collect personal information about your online activities over time and
across different websites, including your use of this Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply
to, and we are not responsible for, the practices of third parties that collect your personal
information.
How Long We Keep Information
The time period for which we keep personal information depends on the purposes for which
we collected it. In all cases we keep it for as long as necessary to fulfil those purposes. We
will then delete this personal information unless we are required to preserve your personal

data in connection with litigation, investigations and proceedings, or if a longer retention
period is required or permitted by applicable law.
Governing Law
This Privacy Policy forms part of our Terms of Use and as such shall be governed by and
construed in accordance with the laws of the state of New York, as further provided in the
Terms of Use.
Information for EU Residents
TPG Europe, LLP is the data controller in respect of personal information collected through
the Site.
We process your personal information for the purposes described above on the basis that it is
necessary for our legitimate interests in operating, managing and improving the Site. We
may use your personal information to send direct marketing only where you have provided
your consent or otherwise when we are permitted by applicable law to do so.
If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), we comply with applicable legal
requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of personal information to
recipients in countries outside of the EEA and Switzerland. In all such cases, we will only
transfer your personal information if:
    •   The country to which the personal information will be transferred has been granted a
        European Commission adequacy decision;
    •   The recipient of the personal information is located in the U.S. and has certified to the
        US-EU Privacy Shield Framework; or
    •   We have put in place appropriate safeguards in respect of the transfer, for example the
        EU Model Contracts.
You may request a copy of the safeguards that we have put in place in respect of transfers of
personal data by contacting us as described in the “How to Contact Us About Privacy
Matters” section below.
If you are located in the EEA or Switzerland, subject to applicable law, you may have the
following rights in relation to personal information that we hold about you:
    •   To request confirmation of whether we process personal information relating to you
        and, if so, to request a copy of that personal information;
    •   To request that we rectify or update your personal information that is inaccurate,
        incomplete or outdated;
    •   To request that we erase your personal information in certain circumstances, such as
        where we collected personal information on the basis of your consent and you
        withdraw your consent;

    •   To request that we restrict the use of your personal information in certain
        circumstances, such as while we consider another request that you have submitted, for
        example a request that we update your personal information;
    •   Where you have given us consent to process your personal information, to withdraw
        your consent; and
    •   To request that we provide a copy of your personal information to you in a structured,
        commonly used and machine readable format in certain circumstances.
    •   To object to certain of our data processing, such as for direct marketing purposes.
If you are located in the EEA and you wish to exercise any of your data protection rights or if
you consider that we have processed your personal information in violation of applicable law,
please contact us as detailed in the “How to Contact Us About Privacy Matters” section
below.
If you consider that we have processed your personal information in violation of applicable
law and failed to remedy such violation to your reasonable satisfaction, you may also lodge a
complaint with the data protection supervisory authority in your country.
How to Contact Us About Privacy Matters
If you would like to contact us for any reason concerning our privacy practices, please email
us at webmaster@tpg.com.
Updates to This Privacy Policy
We may change or update portions of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you.
Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the
Privacy Policy. The revision date appearing on the first page of this Privacy Policy
underneath the title will identify the date of the last update or revision.
Exceptions to This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies only to the public sections of the Site. If you are permitted access
to private areas, the terms of your subscription agreement will control our use of provided
information.
